var quiz = { "EXAM" : [
	{
		"id" : 1,
		"question" : "Which of the following is the definition of chain of command?",
		"options" : [
			{"a": "The succession of commanding officers from a superior to a subordinate through which command is exercised", 
			 "b":"", 
			 "c":"", 
			 "d":""}
			],
		"answer":"The succession of commanding officers from a superior to a subordinate through which command is exercised",
		"score":0,
		"status": ""
	},
	{
		"id" : 2,
		"question" : "What is the primary objective of operational risk management?",
		"options" : [
			{"a": "To avoid unnecessary risks", 
			 "b":"", 
			 "c":""}
			],
		"answer":"To avoid unnecessary risks",
		"score":0,
		"status": ""
	},
	{
		"id" : 3,
		"question" : "Who establishes policy, assigns responsibilities, and prescribes procedures for personnel readiness?",
		"options" : [
			{"a": "Secretary of Defense", 
			 "b":"", 
			 "c":""}
			],
		"answer":"Secretary of Defense",
		"score":0,
		"status": ""
	},
	{
		"id" : 4,
		"question" : "In MCDP-1, Warfighting, war is defined as which of the following?",
		"options" : [
			{"a": "A violent clash of interests between or among organized groups characterized by the use of military force", 
			 "b":""
			}
			],
		"answer":"A violent clash of interests between or among organized groups characterized by the use of military force",
		"score":0,
		"status": ""
	},
	{
		"id" : 5,
		"question" : "Which military Service is the United States' principal air and space force?",
		"options" : [
			{"a": "The Air Force", 
			 "b":"",
			 "c":"",
			 "d":"",
			}
			],
		"answer":"The Air Force",
		"score":0,
		"status": ""
	},
	{
		"id" : 6,
		"question" : "Which of the following is a characteristic of the nature of war?",
		"options" : [
			{"a": "The human dimension", 
			 "b":"",
			 "c":"",
			}
			],
		"answer":"The human dimension",
		"score":0,
		"status": ""
	},
	{
		"id" : 7,
		"question" : "Which element of the MAGTF is composed of the commander, general or executive and special staff sections, headquarters section, and requisite communications support, intelligence, and reconnaissance forces necessary to accomplish the mission?",
		"options" : [
			{"a": "Command element", 
			 "b":"",
			 "c":"",
			}
			],
		"answer":"Command element",
		"score":0,
		"status": ""
	},
	{
		"id" : 8,
		"question" : "Which term is defined as the authority that a commander in the Armed Forces lawfully exercises over subordinates by virtue of rank or assignment?",
		"options" : [
			{"a": "Command", 
			 "b":"",
			 "c":"",
			}
			],
		"answer":"Command",
		"score":0,
		"status": ""
	},
	{
		"id" : 9,
		"question" : "is a clear and concise expression of the purpose of the operation and the desired military end state. It supports mission command, provides focus to the staff, and helps subordinate and supporting commanders act to achieve the commander's desired results without further orders, even when the operation does not unfold as planned.",
		"options" : [
			{"a": "Commander's intent", 
			 "b":"",
			 "c":"",
			}
			],
		"answer":"Commander's intent",
		"score":0,
		"status": ""
	},
	{
		"id" : 10,
		"question" : "Which of the following is the correct location of I MEF?",
		"options" : [
			{"a": "Camp Pendleton, California", 
			 "b":"",
			 "c":"",
			}
			],
		"answer":"Camp Pendleton, California",
		"score":0,
		"status": ""
	},
	{
		"id" : 11,
		"question" : "Which of the following terms is defined as the shared world view and social structures of a group of people that influence their actions and choices?",
		"options" : [
			{"a": "Culture", 
			 "b":"Ethnicity",
			 "c":"Race",
			 "d":"Climate",
			}
			],
		"answer":"Culture",
		"score":0,
		"status": ""
	},
	{
		"id" : 12,
		"question" : "Which of the following is the typical ground combat element for a MEB?",
		"options" : [
			{"a": "Regiment", 
			 "b":"Platoon",
			 "c":"Company",
			 "d": "Battalion",
			}
			],
		"answer":"Regiment",
		"score":0,
		"status": ""
	},
	{
		"id" : 13,
		"question" : "Which of the following are the key factors of culture?",
		"options" : [
			{"a": "Those aspects of culture that influence the outcome of a military operation and, conversely, the military actions that influence the culture of an area of operations", 
			 "b":"The succession of commanding officers from a superior to a subordinate through which command is exercised",
			 "c":"Culture is varied, over time, over space, and among individuals.,Culture is fluid and dynamic.,Culture is shared.",
			 "d":"The primary staff officer for all matters on training, plans, operations, and organization",
			}
			],
		"answer":"Culture is varied, over time, over space, and among individuals.,Culture is fluid and dynamic.,Culture is shared.",
		"score":0,
		"status": ""
	},
	{
		"id" : 14,
		"question" : "Which of the following are characteristics of the nature of war? Select all that apply.",
		"options" : [
			{"a": "Chief of Staff U.S. Air Force,Chief of the National Guard Bureau", 
			 "b":"Uncertainty,Fluidity,Disorder,Physical, moral, and mental forces",
			 "c":"Economy,Social structure,Political structure,Belief system",
			 "d":"Secretary of the Air Force,Secretary of the Army,Secretary of the Navy",
			}
			],
		"answer":"Uncertainty,Fluidity,Disorder,Physical, moral, and mental forces",
		"score":0,
		"status": ""
	},
	{
		"id" : 15,
		"question" : "Which of the following are members of the Joint Chiefs of Staff? Select all that apply.",
		"options" : [
			{"a": "Chief of Staff U.S. Air Force,Chief of the National Guard Bureau", 
			 "b":"Uncertainty,Fluidity,Disorder,Physical, moral, and mental forces",
			 "c":"Secretary of the Air Force,Secretary of the Army,Secretary of the Navy",
			 "d":"Economy,Social structure,Political structure,Belief system",
			}
			],
		"answer":"Chief of Staff U.S. Air Force,Chief of the National Guard Bureau",
		"score":0,
		"status": ""
	},
	{
		"id" : 16,
		"question" : "Which of the following is the largest MAGTF?",
		"options" : [
			{"a": "Marine expeditionary force (MEF)", 
			 "b":"",
			 "c":"",
			}
			],
		"answer":"Marine expeditionary force (MEF)",
		"score":0,
		"status": ""
	},
	{
		"id" : 17,
		"question" : "Which of the following are primary civilian leaders within the DOD",
		"options" : [
			{"a": "Secretary of the Air Force,Secretary of the Army,Secretary of the Navy", 
			 "b":"",
			 "c":"",
			}
			],
		"answer":"Secretary of the Air Force,Secretary of the Army,Secretary of the Navy",
		"score":0,
		"status": ""
	},
	{
		"id" : 18,
		"question" : "Which of the following is the most important of the troop leading steps?",
		"options" : [
			{"a": "Supervise", 
			 "b":"",
			 "c":"",
			}
			],
		"answer":"Supervise",
		"score":0,
		"status": ""
	},
	{
		"id" : 19,
		"question" : "Which of the following best describes the responsibilities of the S-3?",
		"options" : [
			{"a": "The primary staff officer for all matters on training, plans, operations, and organization", 
			 "b":"",
			 "c":"",
			}
			],
		"answer":"The primary staff officer for all matters on training, plans, operations, and organization",
		"score":0,
		"status": ""
	},
	{
		"id" : 20,
		"question" : "Which paragraph of the five paragraph order contains the leader's description of his or her plan for accomplishing the unit's mission?",
		"options" : [
			{"a": "Execution", 
			 "b":"",
			 "c":"",
			}
			],
		"answer":"Execution",
		"score":0,
		"status": ""
	}
	]
}
